RADOSLAV **BUKOV**

Software Engineer







> +359 877 787 997



🔁 <u>radoslaw.bukow@gmail.com</u>



🏠 Smolyan, Bulgaria



https://radoslavbukov.eu



in www.linkedin.com/in/radoslav-bukov-b0a62183



https://github.com/RadoslavBukov



∰ TECHNICAL SKILLS



SOFT SKILLS



LANGUAGES



Experienced and highly trained engineer with 9+ years of proven experience in the field of Automation in Automotive industry. Strong understanding of Computer systems, PLC programming, Automatisation and Control systems, Mechatronics and etc. Proven capability to work independently or as a part of a team. Excellent leadership and communication skills. High interest and commitment to professional development and learning opportunities. Last couple of years with strong interest and dedication in Web Development, Backend with Python and Django, and Frontend with JavaScript, HTML & CSS



EDUCATION

Python Web Developer

Software University 2021 - 2023

Master Automation

Brno University of Technology 2014 - 2014

Master Automation

Technical University 2013 - 2015

Bachelor Automation

Technical University 2009 - 2013



EXPERIENCE

Head of Automatisation Department

Hronovsky

2020 - Present

- Manage, develop and support the software development team.
- Design, planning and software development of new projects.
- Installation, setup and develop specialized automated devices.

Head of Automatisation Department

2016 - 2020

- Manage, develop and support the software development team.
- · Design, planning and software development of new projects.
- Installation, setup and develop specialized automated devices.

Automation engineer

Kostal

2014 - 2016

- Update, maintain and implement improvements in PLC software.
- Installation, setup and develop specialized automated devices such as PLC, Visual systems, Industrial robots, Electronic sensors and others.

CERTIFICATES

- Lean Six Sigma Green Belt
- Leadership and comunnication skills
- Time management
- C# Programming Basics
- Python Programming Basics
- Python Fundamentals
- Python Advanced
- Python OOP
- Python Web Basics
- Python Web Frameworks Django
- Python HTML & CSS
- Python JavaScript Front-end
- Root Cause Analysis
- Staubli: Maintenance TS, TX/SC8C Level 1
- Mitsubishi Robot Advanced Training